mydestinationinfo.com 2012-11-25

# Privacy Policy My Destination

**Data Protection and Privacy**

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 it is confirmed that the proprietor of the website located at [http://www.mydestination.com](http://www.mydestination.com/) (the "Website") is MYDESTINATION.COM Limited, Acre House, 11/15 William Road, London NW1 3ER, United Kingdom ("MY DESTINATION").

MY DESTINATION is committed to protecting the privacy of users of the Website ("you," "your") and sets out its Privacy Policy below in compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998. In general, you can access and browse this Website without identifying who you are or revealing any personal data about yourself. MY DESTINATION will ensure that any personal data received from you will be processed in accordance with the eight principles of the Data Protection Act 1998.

**Collection of Personal Data**

The Website allows you to access and use a range of information relating to travel destinations, including information relating to businesses offering goods and services relating to travel or otherwise, and to access and use third party portals such as portals for searching for and booking services such as hotel accommodation, restaurants, car rentals, flights, entertainment tickets and other services.

MY DESTINATION may collect certain personal data from you via the Website if you choose to submit it to MY DESTINATION via forms completed by you on the Website. Personal data about you may also be collected by MY DESTINATION if you contact MY DESTINATION with queries or to request further information about the Website or any other matter.

The types of personal data which MY DESTINATION may collect from you in the ways referred to above when using the Website may include name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, demographic information and contact preferences.

MY DESTINATION does not store credit card details. Any transactions completed on third party websites are subject to their privacy policies and terms & conditions.

In relation to certain third party portals to which MY DESTINATION provides access on the Website for searching for and booking services such as hotel accommodation, restaurants, car rentals, flights, entertainment tickets and other services, certain additional personal data may be collected by the relevant third party which may include financial data, and debit or credit card details through a separate third party website. Such data is not collected or stored by MY DESTINATION, and MY DESTINATION will have no liability or responsibility with respect to any such personal data submitted by you in this way to such third parties. You should refer to the relevant third party's own privacy policy for further information (see Links below).

**Purpose Specification**

As noted above, MY DESTINATION may collect your personal data for the purpose of contacting you about queries you may have or information or materials which you may provide to MY DESTINATION via the Website. Specifically, MY DESTINATION may use your personal data to set up records for the provision of MY DESTINATION information to you. MY DESTINATION may also use your personal data to better understand who uses our Website and the pages they access so as to be able to improve the Website and the types of information and data provided to users in general via the Website from time to time.

In addition, from time to time, MY DESTINATION may also use your personal data to contact you for market research or user care survey purposes or to let you know about other websites and services MY DESTINATION may be able to provide to you, or to provide you with newsletters, details of special offers or similar. MY DESTINATION will always give you the opportunity to opt-out of such communications.

Only if you _expressly_ grant MY DESTINATION the right to share your personal data with other organisations, institutions and authorities (including by sale or provision of access to a database containing your personal data) by expressly indicating this at the time you provide the information to MY DESTINATION, then MY DESTINATION may disclose your personal data to other organisations, institutions and authorities, subject to your other rights referred to in this Privacy Policy.

Otherwise, MY DESTINATION will ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to other organisations, institutions and authorities unless specifically required by law.

Furthermore, MY DESTINATION will not collect information about you from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations.

If MY DESTINATION transfers management, ownership or hosting of the Website to a third party, you agree that MY DESTINATION may also transfer your personal data and any other information about you to such third party without your further or additional permission, provided that such third party agrees to the same terms of this Privacy Policy.

You hereby agree to and authorise MY DESTINATION to use the personal data you provide to MY DESTINATION for the above purposes. If MY DESTINATION would like to use your personal data for a purpose other than those above, MY DESTINATION will request your express permission first.

**Security**

Personal data provided by you to MY DESTINATION via the Website or otherwise will not be transmitted via secure transmission methods, unless otherwise indicated on the Website. It may be that where you access third party websites (including accessing third party portals for searching for and booking services such as hotel accommodation, restaurants, car rentals, flights, entertainment tickets and other services) you may be required by the relevant third party to provide further personal data which may include debit and credit card data. In the latter case, MY DESTINATION has no involvement with and will not be liable or responsible for such data collection and with respect to security, you should check with the relevant third party to whom you provide your personal data as to whether an encrypted and secure transmission method will be employed to protect such personal data).

You should note that even where personal data is transmitted via the Internet in encrypted form there can be no absolute guarantee that any information carried over the Internet is secure. Information and data transmitted via the Internet may be intercepted by third parties, lost, redirected, corrupted and changed.

Once MY DESTINATION has collected your personal data, MY DESTINATION will employ reasonable security measures in the storage of your personal data to guard against any unauthorised access to or disclosure of your personal data and wherever possible MY DESTINATION will use reasonable security software and secure login procedures.

**Links**

Parts of the Website may contain hyperlinks, banner or panel advertising or icons which upon clicking enable a direct link to third party websites, web pages or portals. This includes the portals accessible on the Website for searching for and booking services such as hotel accommodation, restaurants, car rentals, flights, entertainment tickets and other services. If you use these hyperlinks, banners or panel advertising or icons you will leave this Website immediately and you will be responsible for this action. When you access a third party website, web page or portal you acknowledge and agree that MY DESTINATION does not control the content of such third party websites, web pages or portals and MY DESTINATION is not be responsible or liable for the privacy practices of the relevant third party website, web page or portal.

The privacy policies of each website, web page or portal that you access via hyperlink from the Website will govern the privacy practice of the relevant website, web page or portal and you are encouraged to read such privacy policies immediately upon access thereto. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those third party websites hyperlinked to the Website. Third party websites may send their own cookies to users, collect personal data, or solicit personal data and you acknowledge that MY DESTINATION has no control over such activities.

**Automatic Collection of Personal Data**

Subject to the provision on cookies below, MY DESTINATION has not set up the Website to automatically collect or store personal data about you other than by logging your IP address. An IP address is a string of computer code which identifies your PC and tells the Internet that you are connected to it. This information is not retained after you have logged off. MY DESTINATION does not connect information automatically logged in this way with personal data about you or any specific individuals.

MY DESTINATION may use cookies for collecting data about you on the Website. Cookies are messages given to an Internet browser by an Internet server. The browser in a text file called cookie.txt then stores the message. Each time the browser requests a page from the server, this message is sent back. A cookie's main objective is to identify users and personalise their website visit by customising web pages for them, for example by welcoming them by name next time they visit the same website.

**Subject Access Requests**

Under the Data Protection Act 1998, MY DESTINATION must provide you with a readable copy of all personal data which MY DESTINATION holds about you, within 40 days of receiving your written request for such copies (a subject access request). The Data Protection Act 1998 allows MY DESTINATION to charge a fee of up to �10 pounds for this. Evidence to prove your identity (for example passport, driver's licence and/or current bills) will be required before any personal data held by MY DESTINATION will be disclosed to you. To make a subject access request contact MY DESTINATION on the contact details below.

**Updating Personal Data**

If the personal data which MY DESTINATION holds about you is inaccurate in any way, where appropriate, you may have the data completed, rectified, amended and/or deleted. You should contact MY DESTINATION to update any of your personal data or to request access to your personal data via:

Address

Subject Access Request  
MY DESTINATION  
Acre House, 11/15 William Road,  
London NW1 3ER, United Kingdom 

MY DESTINATION reserves the right to refuse to provide you with a copy of any of your personal data, subject to the Data Protection Act 1998. If MY DESTINATION refuses your request, it will give you reasons for its refusal.

**Amendment to this Privacy Policy**

MY DESTINATION may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time and such amendments will apply by MY DESTINATION publishing the amended Privacy Policy on the Website. Regardless of any changes made to this Privacy Policy, MY DESTINATION will always use your personal data in accordance with the current Privacy Policy, unless you give your express consent for MY DESTINATION to do otherwise.

**Governing Law**

This Privacy Policy will be governed by English law and the parties hereby submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts.

"Living on Earth is expensive, but it does include a free trip around the sun every year" \- Unknown
